Guide to the Civil War Stereographs 1861-1865 PR 65-1
New-York Historical Society
- Bridge Construction Corp. at Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 801-1)
  Bridge Construction Corp. at Alexandria, Virginia.
- Gov't barns at Alexandria (Item 801-2)
  Interior of barn, soldiers moving bales of hay or straw, Alexandria, Virginia.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 801-3)
  Alexandria, Virginia from a high vantage, trains in the foreground, slave dealer and houses beyond.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., May 24, 1861. (Item 801-4)
  Slave pen with soldiers and a wagon in front, Alexandria, Virginia.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., May 24, 1861. (Item 801-5)
  Slave pen with soldiers and a horse drawn wagon in front., Alexandria, Virginia.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 801-6)
  Interior of slave trader's in Alexandria, Va., with soldier, others behind grate.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865 (Item 801-7)
  African-American woman standing outside the slave pen in Alexandria, Virginia.
- The Marshall House, Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 801-8)
  Men on the steps and in front of the Marshall House, Alexandria, Virginia.
- Slave pen, Alexandria, Va., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 801-9)
  Slave pen with soldiers and a horse drawn wagon in front, Alexandria, Virginia.
- B'dway [Broadway] Landing on Appomattox., ca. 1861-ca. 1865 (Item 802-1)
  Pontoon bridge at Broadway Landing, Virginia on the Appomattox River.
- Pontoon bridge on the Appomattox river, near Broadway landing, Va., [ca. 1865] (Item 802-2)
  Pontoon bridge on the Appomattox River, near Broadway Landing, Virginia.
- Pontoon bridge on the Appomattox river, near Broadway landing, Va., [ca. 1865] (Item 802-3)
- House where Gen Lee signed Capitulation papers., [ca. 1865] (Item 802-4)
  McLean's house, two story house, with veranda, fence, women sitting on steps. Surrender made in the front left room.
- McLean's House, Where Lee Surrendered., [ca.1865], published later (Item 802-5)
  View of McLean House behind trees and fence.
- [Remains on battlefield of Bull Run], [after 1861] (Item 803-1)
  Remains (bones) on battlefield of Bull Run.
- Sherman's Battery, as it appeared on its return from the Battle of Bull Run., [ca. 1861] (Item 803-2)
  Group of battery wagons and soldiers, on road in front of unmarked building. Large photographic defect in left hand picture.
- Bull Run Battlefield, Va., [after 1861] (Item 803-3)
  Expanse of battlefield, an empty field with shrubbery; a few houses in the background on a hillside.
- Sudley's Ford, Bull Run., [ca. 1861] (Item 803-4)
  Seven men on horseback crossing a creek. Group of four children in the foreground on near side of creek.
- Sudley's Ford and Church, Bull Run., [ca. 1861] (Item 803-5)
  Brick foundation or bunker on river's edge, child seated on stairs. Fence, trees and house on a hill across the river.
- Robinson's House, Bull Run., [ca. 1861- a. 1865] (Item 803-6)
  Wooden house with porch, trees in yard.
- Ruins of Mrs. Henry's House, Bull Run., [after 1861] (Item 803-7)
  Ruins of a house. Stone fireplace still standing; remains of wooden planks and rubble strewn around fireplace. Soldiers both sitting and standing in vicinity.
- Soldiers' Graves, Bull Run., [ca. 1861] (Item 803-8)
  A soldier looking at soldiers' graves, marked with wooden stakes, next to a creek or marsh.
- Beauregard's Headquarters, Manassas, [ca. 1861-ca.1865] (Item 803-9)
  Two story brick house with tree-lined walkway to front door, people on front steps.
- The new bridge at Bull Run, built by M'Dowell's engineers, [ca. 1861] (Item 803-10)
  Wooden plank bridge, man walking across.
- View on Bull Run., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 803-11)
  View down a river with trees on either bank, logs fallen into the water.
- Headquarters Gen'l M'Dowell, (formerly Gen'l Beauregard's), ca. 1861 (Item 803-12)
  Group of covered wagons with horses, tents, the U.S. flag; all camped in an open field near a house.
- Confederate Barracks, Manassas, [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 803-13)
  Four log cabins among trees.
- Our artist at Manassas, 4th July, 1862., July 4, 1862 (Item 803-14)
  Portable photographer's darkroom on wheels, parked among trees, photographer (O'Sullivan?) standing next to it.
- Bull Run Monuments, [ca. 1865] (Item 803-15)
  Group of soldiers in front of stone pyramid topped with a shell.
- Picket Station, Blackburn's Ford, Bull Run., ca.1861-ca.1865, published later (Item 803-16)
  Soldiers sitting, eating, reclining in and around a tent at a reserve picket station near Bull Run.
- Battle of Bull Run. (Item 803-17)
  Engraving or drawing (?) of Battle of Bull Run. Combat scene involving cannons, horses, soldiers, rifles with bayonets. The U.S. flag lies on the ground.
- Battle Field of Cedar Mountain., [after Aug 9, 1862] (Item 804-1)
  Wooden House with stone chimney, many holes caused by cannonballs. A man and horse stand next to the main house. Confederate General Winder was killed here on Aug 9, 1862.
- Group, Officers of the 10th Maine on the battle field of Cedar Mountain., [ca.1862] (Item 804-2)
  5 officers standing in a field, trees in the background.
- Dead horses on battle field of Cedar Mountain. First position of the Confederate forces, from which they were dislodged, [ca.1862] (Item 804-3)
  Four dead horses on battle field of Cedar Mountain.
- Graves on the battle field of Cedar Mountain, where a large number of Union soldiers were buried., [ca.1862] (Item 804-4)
  Men standing near graves in a field; many pieces of wood are strewn in the foreground.
- Battery fording a tributary of the Rappahannock on the day of the Battle of Cedar Mountain., [Aug 9, 1862] (Item 804-5)
  Soldiers on horseback, foot and in horse-drawn wagons crossing a small river.
- Culpepper [sic] Court House. Group of Confederates, captured at the Battle of Cedar Mountain, at the window., [ca.1862] (Item 804-6)
  Two-story brick court house with portico. Men gathered under the portico and in the upper front window. Men also lounge in front of another building in the foreground.
- City Point, [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-1)
  View of railroad tracks leading to a port with many boxes of stacked cargo. The masts of ships rise above the cargo and a wooden pier and building are visible to the right.
- Gen'l Grant's Headquarters. City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-2)
  Men standing outside a small one story wood house with hitching post in front.
- [View of City Point (Va.) showing men on a pier.], [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-3)
  A group of men standing on a pier, a ship anchored nearby.
- Lieut.-Gen. Grant at his Headquarters, City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865], published later (Item 805-4)
  Grant seated in a chair, with papers, underneath an open-air shelter. Another man stands to his right.
- View of City Point, Va. showing barges, transports, &c., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-5)
  View of port with docked ships and more on the horizon. A covered wagon and a man on horseback are in the foreground.
- View of City Point, Va. showing barges, transports, &c., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-6)
- [View of City Point, Va. showing supplies, men, ships], [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-7)
  View of the port of City Point, Va. showing supplies, men, ships.
- The James River at City Point, [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-8)
  View of the port of City Point, Va. showing ships, cargo, wagons.
- The landing at City Point, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-9)
  View of wharves at City Point, Va. showing smokestacks and ships.
- General Hospital Wharf, army of the James, at City Point, all the wounded take ship here for the North., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-10)
  Steamboat at end of a wharf.
- New ordnance wharf at City Point, Va. built after the great explosion., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 805-11)
  Long view of wharf with docked ship, cargo wagons.
- Soldiers' graves near the General Hospital, City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865], published later (Item 805-12)
  Field of soldiers' graves, some with headstones, with tents in the background
- Army Wagon going to Commissary Depot, City Point, for supplies., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-13)
  Horse-drawn wagon; barrel in foreground.
- Gen. Grant's favorite field horse Cincinnati. Taken at City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-14)
  Man standing next to saddled horse.
- Gen. Grant's favorite field horse Cincinnati. Taken at City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-15)
- Jeff. Davis, one of Gen. Grant's saddle horses. Taken at City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-16)
- Soldiers' Winter Quarters, Army of the Potomac., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-17)
  Group of soldiers standing in front of barracks.
- Serving out rations (small issue), near City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865], published later (Item 805-18)
  Group of soldiers standing on porch and in front of wooden building with barrels lined up on porch and lying on the ground next to a wheelbarrow.
- Lieut. Gen. Grant, wife and son, at his head quarters City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-19)
  Lieut. Gen. Ulysses S. Grant, wife and son in doorway of a house.
- Lieut. Gen. Grant, wife and son, at his head quarters City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-20)
  Lieut. Gen. Ulysses S. Grant, wife and son in doorway of head quarters building.
- Brig. Gen. Rawlins, Wife and Child, at Gen. Grant's Head Quarters, City Point, Va., [ca. 1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-21)
  Brig. Gen. John A. Rawlins, wife and daughter, in doorway of head quarters building.
- Lieut. Gen. Grant, at his Head Quarters, City Point, Va., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 805-22)
  Ulysses S. Grant leaning on a tree, outside of a tent.
- View of City Point Landing, James River, Va., July 5, 1864 (Item 805-23)
  View of a port area with stacks of cargo in barrels, horse-drawn wagons and tents.
- View at City Point, James River, Va., Dock in foreground, July 5, 1864. (Item 805-24)
  Several ships at dock, railroad tracks and moving train in foreground.
- Docks at City Point, James River, Va., July 5, 1864. (Item 805-25)
  View of docks showing ships, railroad tracks, horse-drawn wagons, roofs of nearby buildings.
- Railroad Docks at City Point, James River, Va., July 5, 1864. (Item 805-26)
  Docks with railroad tracks in foreground; ships coming into dock.
- View from hill above City Point Landing, James River, Va., [ca.1864] (Item 805-27)
  Three men grouped outside a tent on a hilltop, one possibly the photographer, port below.
- View of the ruins from the hill above the landing at City Point, James River, after the explosion of 9th August, 1864. (Item 805-28)
  Building in ruins, tents set up around periphery, ships on river in the background.
- Scene at City Point, Va., [ca. 1864], published later (Item 805-29)
  Railroad tracks, with train in foreground, and storehouses at City Point port.
- Scene at City Point, Va., [ca. 1864], published later (Item 805-30)
- General Grant's Horse "Cincinnati.", March, 1865, published later (Item 805-31)
- Professor Lowe observing the battle of Fair Oaks, Va., from his balloon., [June 1862], published later (Item 806-1)
  Man in midair in a hot-air balloon basket, many men holding the ropes on the ground.
- Prof. Lowe replenishing the Balloon from the Balloon Constitution., [June 1862], published later (Item 806-2)
  Hot-air balloon Intrepid being refilled with air in a field.
- Professor Lowe inflating Balloon Intrepid to reconnoiter Battle of Fair Oaks., [June1862] (Item 806-3)
  Hot-air balloon being inflated, crowd watches.
- Gibson's Battery of Horse Artillery, [June1862] (Item 806-4)
  Group of soldiers on horses, horses also pulling artillery carts.
- Benson's [i.e. Gibson's] Battery of Horse Artillery, near Fair Oaks, June 1862 (Item 806-5)
- Front view of old frame house, orchard, and well, at Seven Pines, over 400 were buried here after the battle of Fair Oaks., [June 1862] (Item 806-6)
  Soldiers gathered around howitzers, two frame houses in background, and in the distance, Sickles Brigade in line of battle.
- Redoubt thrown up by M'Carthy near the extreme front., [June 1862] (Item 806-7)
  Log and dirt bunker shielding soldier with artillery.
- Quarles house, near Fair Oaks station, where a large number of the dead were buried., [June 1862] (Item 806-8)
  Men standing and sitting among trees in front of a two story wooden house.
- Fort Sumner, near Susan Clark's house, Fair Oaks., [June 1862] (Item 806-9)
  Soldiers with cannons behind a bunker of sandbags.
- Frame house on Fair Oaks battle field used as a hospital by Hooker's Division., [June 1862] (Item 806-10)
  Two-story wooden frame house with many men gathered in and around it.
- [Frame house on Fair Oaks battle field used as a hospital by Hooker's Division.], [June 1862] (Item 806-11)
- A Battery of "Flying Artillery.", [June 1862], published later (Item 806-12)
  Group of soldiers on horses, horses also pulling artillery carts, including the commanding officer, Horatio Gibson.
- Fair Oaks Station, Va., [June 1862], published later (Item 806-13)
  Soldiers gathered around howitzers, two frame houses in background, Sickles Brigade in background.
- Fort Sumner, near Fair Oaks, Va., 1862., [June] 1862, published later (Item 806-14)
  Soldiers manning light artillery behind a bunker, infantry in background.
- Camp Hamilton near Fortress Monroe Va., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-1)
  Encampment of soldiers in tents at Fort Monroe.
- Camp scene, Fortress Monroe., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-2)
  Group of men seated around a table, drinking, outside a tent, Fort Monroe.
- Fortress Monroe [soldiers dining]., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-3)
  Soldiers dining around a table, in a tent at Fort Monroe.
- Fortress Monroe [men dining on box ], [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-4)
  Soldiers eating and drinking on a table made from box labeled "N.C. staff mess, 5th Regt., NYS[I?]."
- Fortress Monroe [Exterior view, soldiers stand guard on bank.], [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-5)
  Exterior view of Fort Monroe, soldiers stand guard on bank.
- Fortress Monroe [Large cannon, soldier attending, inside fort walls.], [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-6)
  Large cannon, soldier attending, inside the walls of Fort Monroe.
- Bridge at Hampton, Va., burned by the rebels on the arrival of Col. Duryee's 5th Regiment Zouaves at Camp Butler, near Fortress Monroe, Va., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-7)
  Demolished bridge, soldiers standing on and around it, large, columned houses visible in background.
- Scene at Camp Butler, near Fortress Monroe, Va., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-8)
  Group photo of soldiers [Zouaves?], some displaying guns.
- Bridge and main entrance to Fortress Monroe, Va., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-9)
  Bridge over moat approaching entrance to fort, soldiers stand guard.
- Company E, 5th Regiment N.Y. Zouaves, Colonel Duryee, at Camp Butler, near Fortress Monroe, Va., [between ca.1862-ca.1864] (Item 807-10)
  Group of soldiers at alert, guns with bayonets on their shoulders.
- View of lower end of Fredericksburg, February, 1863. (Item 808-1)
  View of two-story brick and wooden houses and a mill with waterwheel, from opposite bank of Rappahannock River.
- Fredericksburg from the Lacy house, March, 1863. (Item 808-2)
  View of town from across the Rappahannock River showing houses, church spires and trees.
- View of Fredericksburg from Tyler's Battery., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 808-3)
  Cannons behind a battery, overlooking river and town.
- Philip's House on fire, Falmouth Station, near Fredericksburg, 14th February, 1863., February 14, 1863 (Item 808-4)
  Three story brick house with porch and three chimneys afire, people watching.
- View of Fredericksburg., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 808-5)
  View of town from opposite bank of river, houses, churches and a mill are visible.
- Burial of dead at Fredericksburgh, Va., [December 15, 1862] (Item 808-6)
  Men prepare to bury the dead, who are draped in tarps or in coffins on the ground.
- The hospital at Fredericksburg, Va., May, 1864., May, 1864, published later (Item 808-7)
  Wounded soldiers gathered around entrance to a brick building, a woman sits in the doorway.
- Wagon train crossing the Rappahannock River., May, 1864, published later (Item 808-8)
  Wagon train crossing the river on a pontoon bridge.
- Burial of the dead., December 15, 1862, published later (Item 808-9)
- Construction Corps at Belle Plains, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-1)
  Tents on hill overlooking a river and port.
- Westover Landing, James River, July 1862. (Item 809-2)
  View through trees of ships at dock, James River, Virginia
- Ruins of Richmond and Petersburg Railroad Bridge across the James., April 5, 1865 (Item 809-3)
  Ruins of railroad bridge over the James River, brick pylons still standing in the river.
- Same View as No. 1040--Chapin's Bluff in the distance., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-4)
  Cannon in bunker overlooking river.
- View of Pontoon Bridge over the James River, [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-5)
  Pontoon bridge over river, with ships beyond it.
- A Picturesque View of Belle Plain Landing, James River., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-6)
  View of river with ships and steamboats, tents on hill above river.
- Signal Tower, Ceppe's Hill, James River., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-7)
  Large multilevel tower, men at top and on ground.
- View of James River Pontoon Bridge, from south side, above Jones' Landing., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-8)
  Pontoon bridge across river, man standing in middle.
- James River Pontoon Bridge, opened for the passage of steamers., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-9)
  Pontoon bridge with gap in middle.
- Celebrated Aikens Landing, where all the Rebel prisoners were exchanged, on the James River near Dutch Gap; the double turreted monitor Omdagua [Onandaga] at anchor in the river., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-10)
  Dock, ship (U.S.S. Onandaga) at anchor in the river.
- Gen. Butler's Dutch Gap canal., [Aug.1864-Dec.1864] (Item 809-11)
  View of canal construction.
- Pontoon boats on the way to Dutch Gap., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 809-12)
  Two boats loaded on wheels, a man sits next to them.
- Pontoon boats on the way to Dutch Gap., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 809-13)
- Dutch Gap Canal. Taken after the bank was blown out. Prof. Maillefert in the foreg'd., [ca.1865] (Item 809-14)
  Canal at Dutch Gap shown leading to river, man sitting on bank.
- Dutch Gap canal and group of soldiers. Taken after the bank was blown out. On the extreme end a portion of the bank remains, which forms a profile, which the soldiers call Jeff. Davis., [ca.1865] (Item 809-15)
  View of canal at Dutch Gap with group of soldiers and an Afro-American man standing on the near bank.
- Dutch Gap canal and group of soldiers. Taken after the bank was blown out. On the extreme end a portion of the bank remains, which forms a profile, which the soldiers call Jeff. Davis., [ca.1865] (Item 809-16)
- Dutch Gap. Soldiers at work inside the dam., Dec. 1864 (Item 809-17)
  View of canal construction at Dutch Gap.
- Dutch Gap canal. Taken after the bank was blown out. James River, Va., [ca.1865] (Item 809-18)
  View of canal at Dutch Gap with pontoon bridge stretching across, soldiers standing on banks.
- The water battery, or battery "Abbot," near Ft. Brady, on James River, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-19)
  Soldiers aim a cannon in a battery above the James River.
- Ft. Brady, James River, Va. View showing Battery ready for action., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-20)
  Soldiers man cannons inside Fort Brady.
- View in water battery, James River, Va. Ready to fire., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-21)
  Soldiers man cannons inside a fort.
- Interior of the Rebel Fort Darling, James River, near Richmond, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-22)
  View of a cannon inside Fort Darling, pointed toward the river.
- Masked battery and obstructions in the James River, Fort Darling, near Richmond, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-23)
  View of river with walkways on bank, hidden battery at Fort Darling.
- Masked battery and obstructions in the James River, Fort Darling, near Richmond, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-24)
- Obstructions in the James River, opposite the Rebel Fort Darling, near Richmond, Va., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-25)
  James River shown with piles of sticks, dirt, other debris.
- Interior of the Rebel Fort Darling, James River, near Richmond, Va. showing magazines, bomb-proofs, and shot and shell., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 809-26)
  Interior of Fort Darling showing cannons, cannonballs and brick fortifications.
- A Pontoon Bridge on the James River., [ca.1861-ca.1865], published later (Item 809-27)
  Pontoon bridge across the James River, man standing in middle.
- Where prisoners were exchanged [Aikens Landing]., [ca.1861-ca.1865], published later (Item 809-28)
- Where prisoners were exchanged [Aikens Landing]., [ca.1861-ca.1865], published later (Item 809-29)
- A Pontoon boat on wheels., [ca.1864-ca.1865], published later (Item 809-30)
- Waiting for exchanged prisoners., [ca.1861-ca.1865], published later (Item 809-31)
  Steamboat "New York" at dock.
- Canvas pontoon bridge across the North Anna, Va., constructed by the 50th N.Y.V. engineers at Jericho Mills, where the 5th Corps under Gen. Warren crossed. View, looking down stream from north bank., [after May 1864] (Item 810-1)
  View down North Anna River showing pontoon bridge, wagons along north bank.
- Jerciho Mills from north bank of North Anna, Va., with canvas pontoon bridge, constructed by 50th N.Y.V. engineers, where the 5th Corps under Gen. Warren crossed 23rd May, 1864., [after May 1864] (Item 810-2)
  View across North Anna River showing pontoon bridge.
- 50th N.Y.V. engineers constructing road at Jericho Mills, on south bank of North Anna, Va. General headquarters' train crossing canvas pontoon bridge in the distance, 24th May, 1864., May 24, 1864 (Item 810-3)
  Group of men constructing road with picks, pontoon bridge behind on North Anna River.
- Jericho Mills, North Anna, Va., looking up stream from south bank, canvas pontoon bridge and pontoon train on opposite bank, 24th May, 1864., May 24, 1864 (Item 810-4)
  View across North Anna River of pontoon bridge, several large wooden buildings on riverbank and beyond.
- Jericho Mills, North Anna, Va., looking up stream from south bank, canvas pontoon bridge and pontoon train on opposite bank., May 24, 1864 (Item 810-5)
- View of Chesterfield bridge on North Anna from rebel redoubt captured by 2d corps under Gen. Hancock, 23rd May, 1864., May 23, 1864 (Item 810-6)
  Cannon behind a bunker, overlooking bridge on the North Anna River.
- Line of breastworks occupied by Union troops on north bank of North Anna, enemies' line of works on south bank, in the distance., [ca.1864-ca.1865] (Item 810-7)
  Soldiers inside a trench, covered with sheets of cloth and wood.
- View of North Anna, with railroad bridge in the distance., [ca.1861-ca.1865] (Item 810-8)
  A group of men swimming in the North Anna River, railroad bridge in the background.
- Pontoon bridges, North Anna, constructed by the 50th N.Y.V. Engineers, below railroad bridge, where a portion of the 2nd Corps, under Gen. Hancock crossed 23rd May, 1864., May 23, 1864 (Item 810-9)
  Two pontoon bridges span North Anna River, two men seated on far bridge.
- A canvas pontoon bridge., [ca. 1864-1865], published later (Item 810-10)
  Pontoon bridge spanning river, soldiers and horses on both banks.
- A Confederate redoubt., [ca.1861-ca.1864], published later (Item 810-11)
  View of a fort interior with cannons, tents, soldiers sitting under the tents.
- A Confederate redoubt., [ca.1861-ca.1864], published later (Item 810-12)
- Our boys in the trenches., [ca.1861-ca.1865], published later (Item 810-13)
- Engineer corps building a road., May 24, 1864, published later (Item 810-14)